travelsignposts.com 2019-01-26

# Travelsignposts Privacy Policy - Travelsignposts

We respect the privacy of those who visit our web site and those who become subscribers. In accordance with this, we have created this policy in order to demonstrate our privacy commitment to our users:

####  What this Privacy Policy Covers

  * This Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personally identifiable information that we collect when you are on our site, and when you use our services. This policy also covers our treatment of any personally identifiable information that third parties share with us.
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of organizations that we do not own or control, or to people that we do not employ or manage.

####  Information We Collect

  * We collect personally identifiable information when you register for an account, when you use our services, and when you visit our pages. We may also receive personally identifiable information from third parties.
  * When you register with us, we ask for your name and email address, and you may also supply other personal details and interests if you want to. Once you register with us and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
  * **Log File Information:** We also automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. This information is not linked to your account and will not be used to identify you.
  *  **Cookies Information:** When you visit our web site, we may send one or more cookies – a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters – to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser and lets us help you log in faster and enhance your navigation through the site. A cookie does not collect personal information about you. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser’s directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of our service may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.
  *  **Clear Gifs Information:** When you use our web site, we may employ clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously. No personally identifiable information from your Company account is collected using these clear gifs. In addition, we may also use clear gifs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients. The information is used to enable more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and make us better for our users.

#### DoubleClick DART cookies

  * We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).  This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”).  The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey).  DART uses “non personally identifiable information”.  It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.  You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting [ http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx)  
  * You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security.  However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites.  This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
  * Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.  Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

#### How We Use This Information

  * We use the personal information you submit to operate, maintain, and provide to you the features and functionality of our web site. Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the web site(for instance, in User Content you post) becomes available to the public. If you remove User Content, copies may remain viewable in cached and archived pages or if other users have copied or stored your User Content.
  * By providing us with your email address you consent to our using the email address to send you Service-related notices, including any notices required by law, in lieu of communication by postal mail. We may also use your email address to send you other messages, such as newsletters, changes to features of the Service, or special offers. If you do not want to receive such email messages, you may opt out by sending an email message to support@travelsignposts.com with the word “No email” in the subject field. Opting out may prevent you from receiving email messages regarding updates, improvements, or offers.
  * We may use certain information about you and/or your User Content without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as analyzing how our web site is used, diagnosing service or technical problems, maintaining security, and personalizing advertisements and promotions.
  * We reserve the right, but have no obligation, to monitor the User Content you post on the site. We have the right to remove any such information or material for any reason or no reason, including without limitation, if in our sole opinion, such information or material violates, or may violate, any applicable law or our Terms of Use Agreement or to protect or defend our rights or property or those of any third party. We also reserve the right to remove information upon the request of any third party.
  * We use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the site; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our service; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and traffic; (e) diagnose or fix technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP; and (f) help you efficiently access your information after you sign in.

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

  *  **Personally Identifiable Information:** We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone.
  * We will only send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:
    * We have your consent to share the information;
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
    * We find that your actions on our web sites violate the Terms of Service
  * We may share your personally identifiable information with third parties solely for the purpose of providing services to you. If we do this, such third parties’ use of your information will be bound by this Privacy Policy. We may store personal information in locations outside the direct control of Company (for instance, on servers or databases co-located with hosting providers).
  * As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or dissolution.
  * Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, we will not disclose personal information to any third party unless required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law, comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates, or investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities; (b) to enforce our Terms of Use, take precautions against liability, to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, to assist government enforcement agencies, or to protect the security or integrity of our site; and (c) to exercise or protect the rights, property, or personal safety of the Company, our users or others.
  *  **Non-Personally Identifiable Information:** We may share non- personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain Company services.
  * We allow other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements on our web site. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on our web site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize the advertising content.
  * We do not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks us to show an advertisement to a certain audience and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they are trying to reach.
  * You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. Our privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such advertisers.

#### How We Protect Your Information

  * We use commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, We make commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.
  * To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your identity before granting you access to your account. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications from us, at all times.

####  Compromise of Personal Information

  * In the event that personal information is compromised as a result of a breach of security, Company will promptly notify those persons whose personal information has been compromised, in accordance with the notification procedures set forth in this Privacy Policy, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

#### Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences

  * We give you the ability to edit your Account Information and preferences at any time, including whether you want us to contact you about new services.
  * You may request deletion of your account by sending an email to support@ travelsignposts.com.

####  Security

  * Your Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security.
  * In certain areas we use industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.

####  Public Forums

  * This site may make chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas become public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

#### Purchasing on the Web site

  * Travel Signposts is an Associate of Amazon.com and information provided during all purchases made on this website from Amazon is protected by Amazon’s Security and Privacy policies.
  * We also offer our own e-books for sale through ClickBank, E-junkie and PayPal, whose privacy and security policies strictly protect any information supplied to them during the purchase process.
  * To purchase items from this website, a purchaser needs to complete an order form that gives us contact information (like their name, email address and delivery address), and financial information (like their credit card numbers) to Amazon and/or PayPal. Credit cards details are protected by SSL encryption. All information is stored in our partners’ secure databases and is only accessible by authorised staff.

####  Chidren’s Privacy

  * Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, we do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to us. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at support@travelsignposts.com.

#### Third Party Advertisements and Technologies

  * We use third-party advertising companies to serve advertisements when you visit our web site. The third-party advertising technology that we use on this site uses information derived from your visits to this site to target advertising within this web site. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on this Site and other websites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed your browser.
  * We also use web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits this site, to learn which banner ads bring users to our web site and to deliver more relevant advertising. You may "opt-out" of certain third party programs by following the instructions located at http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/index.aspx.

####  Notification Procedures

  * It is our policy to provide notifications, whether such notifications are required by law or are for marketing or other business related purposes, to you via email notice, written or hard copy notice, or through conspicuous posting of such notice on our web site page, as determined by us in our sole discretion. We reserve the right to determine the form and means of providing notifications to you, provided that you may opt out of certain means of notification as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Third Parties

  * We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained in them. Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect.
  * Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including those that have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

####  Changes to this Privacy Policy

  * This privacy policy is subject to modification from time to time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Any significant changes to our privacy policy will be announced on our home page. If you do not agree with the changes in our policy you have the ability to remove your account information. This can be done by sending email to support@travelsignposts.com.

####  Questions or Suggestions

  * If you have questions or suggestions complete a feedback form or send an email to support@travelsignposts.com.
